syncapse.com 2012-06-13

# Privacy Policy

_Last Updated: October 3, 2011_

Syncapse Corp. (hereafter referred to as “Syncapse”, “we” or “us”) wants you to fully understand our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information through our websites located at URL: www.Syncapse.com, or any other Syncapse owned website (collectively known as, the “Website” or “Site”). “Personal Information” means information that would allow a party to contact you, or any other information you provide about yourself through the Website, including, for example, your full name, address, telephone number, or email address.  
Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your Personal Information. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and without any notice by posting a revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Any such revision will become effective immediately upon posting. 

##### Information We Collect and How We Use That Information

Our registration forms require users to provide contact information, including name, physical address, company information, website information, website statistics, email address, and similar information. 

We will use your Personal Information to perform the services or to provide the information you have requested. In addition, we may use Personal information collected via this Site to improve the content of our Site, to customize the Site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if you have requested it), for our marketing and research purposes (including a follow-up call or e-mail to obtain your feedback regarding any information or materials you have asked us to provide to you), and for any other purpose specified at the time we collect your Personal Information. In addition, we may make full use of all information acquired through this Site that is not in personally identifiable form. 

Syncapse uses a single crawler that respects industry standards when gathering web data. We use your domain’s robots.txt file to tell us which files we can search and which files to leave alone. You can also control how often we search your site. 

##### Disclosure of Personal Information

We do not share, sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties, except as explained in this Privacy Policy. Although we may disclose aggregated information about the use of our Website, that information does not contain Personal Information. However, we may share Personal Information with: (1) our contractors and service providers we use to support our business, in which case we require such contractors and service providers to agree to treat such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, (2) as may be required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations, or to comply with legal process served on Syncapse, and (3) if Syncapse were to decide to divest its business, to actual or potential purchasers who have provided written assurances that they will handle such information appropriately. 

##### Communications

If you have registered to receive email communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. To Opt-out send an email to [opt-out@Syncapse.com](mailto:opt-out@Syncapse.com). Please reference “Opt-Out” in your subject line and state in the body of the email that you wish to have your name removed from the distribution lists. 

##### Internet Protocol Address

We collect Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses from all visitors to the Website. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Website, analyze trends, track users’ movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Website, and deliver customized, personalized content. 

##### Use of “Cookies”

Cookies are pieces of data created when you visit a site. The cookies set by the Syncapse servers are unique, anonymous numbers. They are stored by your browser on your hard drive. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. If you choose not to accept the cookie, this will affect your access to the majority of facilities available on our Website. 

Although your browser may be set up to allow the creation of cookies, you can specify that you be prompted before a site puts a cookie on your hard disk, so that you can decide whether to allow or disallow the cookie. Alternatively, you can set your computer not to accept any cookie. If you turn cookies off, you will not have access to some features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services may not function properly. 

##### Security

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Log file access is restricted to system administrators while stored on the server. Log files are rotated regularly and archived in a secure location. 

You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this Site may not be secure. 

##### Other websites

Our Website contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website over which Syncapse has no control and will bear no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such websites as their policies may be different from ours. 

##### Children’s Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy rights of children. The Site is intended for adult users over the age of 13. The Site is not designed to attract child users. If we learn that an under-13 user has provided Personal Information on the Site, we will delete such information from our active databases. 

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or your dealings with this Website, or would like to make corrections to Personal Information which you submitted, you can e-mail us at [privacy@Syncapse.com](mailto:privacy@Syncapse.com).
